# **ANTHONY VIDAL**

Las Vegas, NV 89121 | (702) 626-5551 | anthonyvidal3019@gmail.com

## **Professional Summary**

Hello, my name is Anthony. I am a highly driven Cybersecurity student with 3+ years of experience in desktop support management. In addition, I have acquired multiple IT industry certifications. With a strong interest in Networking and Cybersecurity, I have a great desire to learn and grow my skill set. I am currently pursuing a Bachelor of Science in Cybersecurity.

#### **Certifications**

CompTIA Security+
CompTIA Network+
CompTIA A+
CompTIA Project+
ITIL Foundation
EC-Council Certified Encryption Specialist

## **Work History**

**SSCP** 

**Lead IT Specialist** Feb 2021 - Current

Las Vegas Paiute Tribe

Las Vegas, NV

- Diagnosed, repaired, and maintained hardware and software components to ensure the smooth running of all tribal government systems.
- Drove improvements to retail operations, cannabis operations and health clinic operations.
- Created help desk tickets, troubleshot and managed desktop issues.
- Resolved diverse range of technical issues across multiple systems and applications for customers and end-users across various time zones.
- Oversee general IT support for all Tribal operations, including a Health clinic, Nuwu Cannabis operation, Paiute golf resort, and Tribal law enforcement.
- Collaborated with supervisors to escalate and address customer inquiries or technical issues.
- Diagnosed network problems involving combination of hardware, software, power and communications issues.

West Coast Cloud Solutions Garden Grove, CA

- Updated and maintained computer inventory, mobile devices and workstations.
- Removed malware, ransomware and other threats from laptops and desktop systems.
- Responded to support requests from end users and patiently walked individuals through basic troubleshooting tasks.
- Patched software and installed new versions to eliminate security problems and protect data.
- Active Directory
- Sophos Central

PC Technician Feb 2018 - Jun 2019

Fry's Electronics Inc.

Anaheim, CA

- Answered calls and emails at the company's help desk, assisting employees and customers with troubleshooting computer issues.
- Used diagnostic tools to identify hardware failures and replace non-functional components.
- Built custom Desktop's per customers specifications.
- Providing technical support.
- Maintaining hardware and software

Packaging Associate Oct 2016 - Mar 2018

American Apparel La Mirada, CA

- Prepared orders for shipment by inserting associated paperwork, tagging boxes and scanning barcodes to upload package data to tracking system.
- Moved packages to loading area using lift equipment and conveyor systems.
- Achieved production targets by maintaining high productivity levels and communicating effectively with team members regarding orders and fulfillment.
- Accurately measured and weighed packages to review dimensions and verify compliance with specifications.

### **Education**

#### **Bachelor of Science: Cybersecurity And Information Assurance**

05/2022

Western Governors University

Salt Lake City, UT

#### **High School Diploma**

06/2012

Western High School Anaheim, CA